hey what's up everybody today we're
going to talk about finding your Niche
what are the most profitable niches for
coaching membership subscription sites
as well as how do you monetize in
something if you're just starting out
online stay tuned we're going to walk
you through the steps of starting a
$5,000 to $25,000 per month business
that you can build that's sustainable
for those of you that I have not met yet
my name is Jeremiah Kowski and for the
last 21 years I have been helping
coaches mentors trainers course creators
we used to do seminars in DVDs and CDs
and I've built multiple businesses over
$10 million a year in this industry and
I've dedicated my entire working life
and career to this helping people
succeed I've helped thousands of coaches
mentors and course creators succeed and
I want to help you as well even if
you're just starting out and that's
exactly what this video is all about
it's for those that are just starting
out hey if I you know I lost everything
what would I do kind of a thing where
you got to pick a niche that's
profitable you got to find something
that's monetizable so that's one of the
first things is like what will people
actually buy from you now one of the
biggest struggles people have when it's
choosing a niche has to do with they
they don't feel confident that that two
things they can either deliver the
results or that it's going to make them
money and both of these end up making us
spin like a
hamster uncertain what we should be
doing and we're not aware of how to
actually make money with with it you
have to take action and you can't let
the fear of missing out keep you stuck
fomo is one of the biggest reasons why I
meet people they have incredible
knowledge incredible information massive
levels of experience where they can
deliver value that should be making them
millions of dollars as coaches and
they're not even making $5,000 because
they are afraid of picking the wrong
idea it not working out or if they pick
one idea they miss out on another or
they miss out on helping a bunch of
people the other mistake is that they're
trying to help way too many people as
far as this goes okay the other one is
is that they pick a niche that they feel
confident in but it's not monetizable
and it's because they don't feel
confident doing something that actually
is monetizable so here's something else
that I'm going to tell you you can grow
in skill set to move into a different
Niche over time the niche that you
choose today when you start does not
have to be your Forever Niche and this
is one of the biggest mistakes I think
people make is that they're looking for
something that's going to be forever for
them I want you to pick something that's
going to be for the next year and and
and that's a good piece of advice you
might say well gosh when you transition
after a year you're not going to like
throw it all away it's going to be an
incremental transition as far as that
goes here's an example I helped a client
build a business uh in the WordPress
website building space they transitioned
couple years later to social media grew
a huge social media following then they
transitioned from that to Facebook ads
and then from that they actually
transitioned over into wealth creation
and then they transitioned over to just
the stock market and private Equity that
was over the course of I think that was
from 2009 until uh
2019 so that was 20 is that 20 years no
10 years yeah 10 20 years 10 years 10
years they were able to go from this one
Niche and they pretty much transitioned
every 2 and A2 years over to this other
one and now they're one of the leading
experts in the stock market mentoring
space but they started in the website
building space another client they
started in um music at Christian worship
music coaching and now they've
transitioned over to uh small business
coaching as far as that goes and that
was like a 5year transition as far as
that goes because they figured out the
world of business that this person built
a $10
million business and then was able to do
that okay so this is where I see a lot
of people it's like okay they grow they
transition they learn so one of the
biggest things is that if you're ready
to transition to a different Niche you
are going to have to eventually let go
of the fact that some people are going
to drop off some people are going to
fall off I plan on transitioning who I'm
reaching over time and I'm noticing that
just as I'm growing as I'm communicating
better you might notice I'm a lot more
confident today if you've been watching
my videos for a while than I used to be
I believe in myself a lot more I'm a lot
clearer in what I talk about I'm a lot
more direct and organized with my
information all that to say it you you
grow and as you grow things shift and
they change and they turn into other
things that they were different than
where they started okay so that's a good
thing and that's by Design and you want
it to be that way okay don't get stuck
in one thing simply because that's what
people expect of you and that's
something that I I'll encourage
everybody is other people's obligations
are one of the biggest reasons why
people don't make money in a business
because they feel obligated to do what
everybody expects of them even if they
hate it even if it's killing them okay
listen what you promised fulfill those
promises but you can transition and
transition is a good thing from where
you've been to where you want to go that
is more profitable and prioritizing
profit margins is also not a bad thing
as well okay now when you're picking a
niche you want to find something that
you have experienc in one of the biggest
mistakes that people make is they don't
have experience in the niche that
they're picking and they it sounds like
a good idea now there's a caveat to this
I think that you can as you go into a
new niche you might deal with a little
bit of impostor syndrome you might feel
like a fraud initially as far as that
goes you know I myself and when I
transitioned into what I'm doing right
now I had dealt with that impostor
syndrome for a couple of years as far as
that goes until I felt confident enough
to be like okay I'm showing up I feel
great about what I do I feel great about
how I communicate with people how I get
to talk with them and I believe in
myself not because it's just grandiose
in my head but because of the track
record results and what we produced in
people's lives as far as that goes okay
so from there what you want to take is
you want to take your experience and you
want to merge that with what other
people actually want okay so you got to
take your experience this is your XP
this is other people's desires and you
merge these two together and this is
where you find your Niche is where this
is right here and this also should be
what is monetizable so if people want it
you have experience in it and you can
make money with it that is a Sure Fire
way to identify what the right Niche is
now if you're just starting out some of
y'all are like I don't know what I have
experience
in great that's okay I don't know what
people want awesome that's not a that's
not a problem that's where a lot of
people are when they meet me they don't
know what that is and and I sure as
don't know what is monetizable at all
because I don't have experience in
business that's okay that's why people
work with me that's why people become
client of my client growth accelerator
program that's why they join me on the
different events that I do the live
events that we host all the time over at
my website and you can you can check
those out right now we're actually
hosting one on Wednesday uh June 5th
called create and launch your sixf
figure group coaching Community offer
without burnout and the whole idea
behind this is once you know what your
Niche is you want to actually create an
offer that gets people to sign up and
that gets people to register with you
and you got create a lead magnet of some
kind to actually get people to buy from
you just knowing your Niche is like the
is like picking your address as far as
that goes okay so that's one of the
things that we do is we help people in
these Live Events we also have my
coaching program right here the client
growth accelerator program enrollment is
currently closed we're on a waiting list
basis for that okay so as far as this
goes here's what we I like to do to
figure this out is this is where we can
use Ai and if you've not used artificial
intelligence before it's not as scary as
it sounds make an account with chat
gp.com and start playing around with it
and you want to use it to help you
brainstorm ideas so I'm going to walk
you through here real quick how we use
chat GPT to brainstorm ideas for our
Niche and I've walked a ton of people
through this over the years check this
out make me a list and this is right
here inside of chat GPT the free version
will give you this g chat GPT 40 is the
one that we're using here make me a list
of the most profitable online course
course or
coaching
niches that I could run as a recurring
membership around 97 to 197 a month okay
and that's a pretty profitable uh price
range as far as that goes so obviously
Business and Entrepreneurship will
always fall into that range we know that
if you have experience in certain Realms
of business particularly with people
that are starting or in marketing or
scaling those are great niches uh
personal finance and investing financial
planning but this is where health and
wellness is actually one of the most
profitable niches as far as that goes
and this is why I love using AI because
it's really accurate at kind of telling
you all this type of stuff um technology
and coding if you know how to use AI
that's another great profitable Niche
personal development leadership
management public speaking creative arts
and hobbies I know a guy he built a $3
million a year business right here in
this space language learning
relationship coaching that's a huge one
uh lifestyle and personal growth de
developing the lifestyle spiritual
coaching I know a lot of people that do
spirituality coaching and are also very
profitable can you also make me a list
of a 100 unique
niches outside of the realm of the ones
above okay so let's check this out okay
here's 100 unique niches you can ask
chat GPT to give you this information to
help you brainstorm pet training and
Care gardening and urban
farming uh drone piloting so you can see
all of this right here let's just pick
one of these okay let's just pick um
scuba diving and snorkeling you might be
like well why would people pay me for
that we'll check this
out watch
this
brainstorm 20 sub niches for a
profitable coaching business related to
uh we could do introductory courses
Advanced underwater photography and
videography so really it could deal with
like getting into the underwater
photography realm and actually working
in the underwater space is what it would
be it would go beyond just diving and it
would probably have to do with like a
monetization type of a thing as far as
this goes
take take all these ideas and develop 10
ideas for a complete program that could
sell for $2,000 a year that people would
actually pay for and brainstorm as an
expert in this field why people would
pay that much for this info be realistic
okay it's not it's going to be totally
realistic on this check this out
comprehensive scuba diving Mastery
Program underwater photography Master
Class marine
biology uh technical dive deep waterer
exploration course
okay so let's say like you have that
experience scuba diving doesn't sound
like a profitable niche as far as that
goes but now we're seeing how literally
you could actually find specific people
that are looking for that area right
there and they're willing to make a
significant financial investment in the
thing that you're wanting to show them
and how to do so the AI gives us some
great input as far as how to develop out
and choose a niche as far as that goes
here's what we got to figure out when
you're choosing a niche it's not about
what you're going to teach it's not
about the topic it's
about
who you're going to help why because
people are the ones with the money
people are the ones with the desire and
people are the ones that care about your
experience the topic itself doesn't care
about money desire or experience the
topic itself is purely informational and
as we now have with AI we can see that
information is a dime of dozen you can
just ask AI for lot of information
what's valuable is having an
expert who understands the market that
understands the industry that
understands the activity and then can
help guide and direct people along that
process okay so here's what we would
want to do one of the biggest mistakes
people make now is that they're going to
go out there and they're going to record
all of this content if you use chat GPT
you're going to come up with ideas for
how to create a program or things like
that I would not recommend that you come
out with and create all of this content
what I would recommend that you do is
you do an
experimental uh
alpha or
beta test program where you're going to
get some people gathered together to
test out your program and to see and
gain interest as far as that goes so
there's a couple ways to do this you can
use your organic social media you can
find some experts in that field who are
willing to partner with you especially
if you have a unique product that
doesn't have a lot of offerings in that
space you can negotiate with experts
that might have podcasts or audiences to
promote you for a commission because
maybe they don't have a product and they
want to make a commission off of that so
that's how you could even affiliate that
to get your name out there and do and do
some some promotion that way
okay lots of different options that you
can do you can run paid advertising
campaigns we teach people how to do that
in my accelerator programing in in our
program we walk you through the whole
process of building out your program
marketing it how to create all of the
marketing materials you get feedback and
get to work with me to guide you through
the whole process in a judgment free
space with Incredible people in our
community that are willing to help you
and work with you and come alongside you
to guide you through that whole process
and that's why it's amazing when we see
people that jump in with us is they're
excited by the fact that they can
actually make something tangible out of
the ideas that they have you know an
idea is only worth a little bit if we
don't take action on it okay so let's
come up with our idea we can use AI to
come up with this idea and then what we
want to do is we want to make it
tangibly around what I call the three
most important stages or
steps in building a business in this
space okay because we know that we want
to monetize we have to figure out how to
find
the
people that are looking to do the thing
that we are offering and then we have to
figure out how to promote our offer to
those people okay this can either be
organic this could be through joint
ventures podcast this could be through
advertising and then we have
to
close the sale so find the people
promote our offer to them and then close
the sale and this is where money is
exchanged and most people never even get
to the stage where they even have an
opportunity to close because they never
actually put themselves out there to
promote it because they're afraid and
wondering if they're good enough to be
able to even do that and so they won't
even look where people are or know where
they're at because they're unsure if
they can actually make it
work and all this boils down to is in
between their two ears they're doubting
themselves they're trying to avoid
embarrassment they're trying to avoid
wasting time and they're not quite
sure if they should be doing it and I
meet people hundreds of people every
single day that this is where they're at
and that might be where you're at and I
wanted to tell you this it's it's it's
not your
fault it's not because this is
uncomfortable and most of us have not
ever been trained on how to do this
process and that's normal and it's okay
but we do have to choose to grow if we
want to have a business to be able to
actually do what is uncomfortable
promoting self-promotion feels
uncomfortable right we want people to
tell others about ourselves but can I
tell you this me in this video here
today I am I've self-promoted myself the
whole time on here and I've not done it
awkwardly right I'm I'm I'm sharing
value with people I'm giving incredible
strategy to people on how to get
started and so you have to grow in the
ability to actually be willing to
promote yourself as far as that goes and
close the sale and not feel guilty about
asking for an exchange of money not
feeling
guilty for making money for the things
that you're
doing okay and so to be able to do all
of this the process that we like to use
is we create a lead magnet and then we
can put something together to grow our
email list and an offer that then people
sign up for and then from that offer
they will be sold something there is a
sales process right here but the sales
process is not how you think it is the
right sales process comes together by
connecting with people in a way that's
not salesy it's not sleazy it's not
slimy you're actually providing value to
people and the reason why it sells to
them the right people start to really
like listening to you they enjoy hearing
you they they they connect with it and
they want to know how can I go deeper
with what you're talking about it's very
much a liken to dating I look at all of
this very even similar to the dating
world and one of the biggest things that
I noticed that some people they're
they're uncomfortable they're insecure
even about themselves personally this is
where personal development is such an
important thing to be able to grow in to
be able to figure out what do you want
who are the clients you want how do we
find them how do we promote ourselves to
them and then how do we get those sales
and this is a process that every single
day I'm working with my clients through
I'm training people on I'm walking them
through and I'm showing them step by
step exactly how to do this one of the
number one ways to be able to find the
people is you have to look at where do
they spend the most amount of time okay
so wherever your Niche is do they read
magazines are they listening to certain
podcasts are there certain websites they
visit do they watch certain YouTubers
okay you can promote in front of the
viewers of all these different platforms
are they on Instagram are they on
Facebook are they on Tik Tok What are
they looking up what hashtags are they
searching and then you're going to be
able to show up in front of those
people with your offer that you're
promoting now here's the thing nobody
likes to be sold or promote things and
we know that right but that's where what
you get to do is to promote it you
actually provide real value you take a
portion of what you actually are going
to Market to people and actually what
you're going to sell and you help people
with the beginning stages and the
beginning steps of it and that's what
becomes your irresistible offer okay and
so that's exactly what I'm going to be
teaching here this week during the class
that I'm hosting all about your uh it's
right here over at my
website all about finding your offer
creating and launching a sixf fig group
coaching Community offer and that's one
of the biggest things is if you want to
monetize to make $10,000 $20,000 a month
or more you want to do it in a group
setting not just one-on-one with people
as far as that goes you want to gather a
group of people together and what this
does is this allows you to not have to
burn yourself out to do this whole
process because when you're working with
a group of people you can actually get a
lot more done with a lot less time and a
lot less effort I don't need to talk
individually one-on-one with people
because the same message goes out to the
whole group of people as far as that
goes and so when you learn how to do
this the right way you can become very
very profitable in your business when
you learn how to communicate well when
you learn how to to effectively connect
with people you got to connect with
people when you're coaching them and you
also got to connect with them when you
are selling to people and this process
is a area that that's exactly what I
help people with and that I walk them
through and that I show them and that I
guide them through how to grow in that
you do not have to walk scared through
this okay but sometimes you might have
to do what feels uncomfortable you might
have to learn what you don't know right
now you might have to grow in certain
skill set that is not the norm for you
as far as that goes it wasn't the norm
for me to do any of this in my business
it wasn't the norm for me to do any of
this for years I had helped other people
do this but not in my own business and
so I had to learn how to reach the right
people you got to figure out what is one
specific thing that they need help with
you want to identify problems that
people have when people have
problems you can solve those problems
and the faster you can solve problems
for
people the more likely it is that they
are going to trust you and then want to
work further with you and you want to
find people that are actually serious
and so here's one of the number one
things that you also have to realize is
that when you're marketing or promoting
or finding people for your coaching
business
95% of the people that you are going to
connect with are never going to buy a
thing from
you
okay 95% of of the views that you get on
YouTube 95% of the the likes or shares
that you get on social media so this is
where you got to really learn how to
pump those numbers up and that's where
you got to learn how to communicate in a
way that connects with people that keeps
them listening you're competing against
other
experts that are also masterful
communicators and they're all using
artificial intelligence to get better at
what they're doing better at their craft
and so for you to gain market share you
got to learn how to communicate at a top
tier level and when you can do that you
can take that 5% right here and that 5%
can literally turn into 3,000 people in
a group membership program and these
3,000 people might be paying you $97 a
month as far as that goes like one of
our clients that we had built their
coaching business over $3 million a
year working
5 to 10 hours a week meeting once a week
with a group of 3,000 people around a
very specific Niche topic that was
related to direct sales marketing as far
as that goes okay and so if you can
figure out a topic and then rally a
group of people around you to listen to
you and you're able to be a speaker to
people and they want to hear you as a
speaker and they want to hear your ideas
and ideas go into their brain and it
helps them make
decisions this helps motivate people and
this helps get people to take action
with you and that's how you can become
extremely highly paid this is how you
don't have to struggle to be able to pay
your bills this is how you can be able
to make six and seven figures
consistently is by learning how to
communicate well I didn't know how to
communicate for years I was homeschooled
I was very awkward at communication I
didn't know how to make video content at
all and it took me quite a lot of time
to learn how to do this if I can
accelerate that for you it was getting
out of my own head I had to stop being
worried about what people thought I had
to stop living in the past I had to stop
being so concerned about how I looked to
everybody and learn how to talk and
speak from the heart and connect my
heart with my mind and not let my mind
talk me out of what comes out of my
mouth as far as that goes you know we're
always told think before you speak think
before you say a word well when you
actually train yourself how to this
whole process can happen in real time so
you don't have to hesitate and I think
that's one of the biggest things that we
do is we hesitate we pause we take a lot
of time to take action we take a lot of
time to do the stuff that's actually
going to help us build a business
because we don't want to look a certain
way and we're concerned about managing
how our appearances and our reputation
listen your reput is important manage it
it's great make your character be at a
high level so that people trust you and
they believe in you and they know
exactly who you are when they see you
okay but you can't concern yourself
about what other people think about us
and those are two very different things
okay people are going to judge you
people are going to people call me all
the time bunch of names just ugly names
on social media all the time every day
for videos just like this they'll watch
it and they'll I leave a comment that's
ugly and and and and I just got to let
it roll off because I can't let that
affect me I can't let it bother me I
can't sit there and ruminate and wonder
why do they do that and why do I feel so
stuck by this and how can I make sure
that they never do that again and like
no I got to keep going forward I got to
keep moving forward and I got to I can't
sit in the crap yeah I said it because
that's what it is we end up sitting in
our stuff and we don't actually go out
there to reach the people that are
waiting for us to grow past our
limitations the people that are waiting
for us to grow up out of what has tried
to stop us what has tried to break us
what has tried to keep us stuck in the
starting stages of where we're at it's
time to graduate out of the starting
stages my
friends it's time to graduate to a
higher
level and when you do this
you're able to make a lot of money and
often times it has very little to do
with not knowing what to do most of
y'all know exactly what you want to do
inside of you but you're doubting
yourself ask yourself this what are you
trying to
avoid what do you not want to happen
what are you afraid might happen if you
go out there you put yourself out there
and it doesn't work out as far as that
goes realize everything is a risk and
there's no guarantees in business and
that's okay that's by Design and learn
to embrace risk and learn to embrace
putting yourself out there Corporate
America doesn't teach you this Corporate
America wires your brain to be easily
controlled and manipulated and fearful
and worried about other people's
approval as far as that goes and I find
that when we're so worried about other
people's approval it's called the
addiction to people pleasing we end up
not showing up the way that we need to
in our businesses and so when it comes
to you building a coaching business and
finding your Niche you cannot let the
fear of other people's opinions of you
or you messing up or you making a
mistake or things not being perfect stop
you you got to grow up past that and I
don't mean to be disrespectful saying
that to you at all I know some people
might take offense to that when I say
that but it's why you're not making the
kind of money you want to make in a
business is we got to make a choice and
that choice might look like working with
a therapist through the limitations you
have that choice might look like doing
it scared that choice might look
like moving forward without knowing for
certain what's going to happen next but
can I tell you this if you work with me
if you listen to me if you follow my
content if you subscribe to this channel
I'll stick with you I got your back and
I want to help you succeed and I don't
want you to go out there on your own
you're not on your own when you can work
with me and that's why you're here and I
and I just encourage you keep watching
the videos that I'm putting on YouTube
we got a ton of videos on YouTube for
free we got a ton of podcast episodes
you can check out all on the topics of
everything that people that are just
like you what you need to be able to be
successful make sure to join us for one
of the live events that we're hosting
kind of like the one that we're doing on
Wednesday June 5th I think it'd be great
for you and you know jump into my client
growth accelerator program when we open
the doors to it uh it'll be $200 a month
basically is what it costs it's very
affordable for what you get you get a
complete system that's that is the best
system in my opinion for how to take one
of these businesses be successful and do
the work that's actually going to make
you money not just systems not just
strategies but what's actually going to
bring in cash flow for you all right
that's exactly what I what I live for
and what I love to do is helping people
bring in successful cash flow that
impacts people it impacts their life and
it also impacts the lives of their
clients as far as that goes and so I'd
love to work with you I'd love to be a
part of your team to build that business
with you step by step all right so get
on the waiting list for the accelerator
I'll see you in there when we open the
doors to it all right have a good one
everybody enjoy these videos and we'll
talk soon